var questionsArray = [
  {
    question: "1. What is the primary purpose of JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "Styling web pages",
      "Server-side scripting",
      "Interactive webpage scripting",
      "Database management"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Interactive webpage scripting"
  },
  {
    question: "2. Which keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "let",
      "var",
      "const",
      "variable"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "var"
  },
  {
    question: "3. What does the 'DOM' stand for in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "Document Object Model",
      "Data Object Model",
      "Dynamic Object Management",
      "Document Oriented Model"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Document Object Model"
  },
  {
    question: "4. What is the purpose of the 'addEventListener' method in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "To modify an element's style",
      "To attach an event handler to an element",
      "To create a new HTML element",
      "To remove an element from the DOM"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To attach an event handler to an element"
  },
  {
    question: "5. What is the difference between 'let' and 'const' in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "Scope",
      "Mutability",
      "Hoisting",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Mutability"
  },
  {
    question: "6. How do you check the type of a variable in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "typeOf",
      "varType",
      "typeof",
      "variableType"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "typeof"
  },
  {
    question: "7. What is 'NaN' in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "Not a Number",
      "Null and Negligible",
      "Number and Null",
      "Not an Null"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Not a Number"
  },
  {
    question: "8. Which method is used to remove the last element from an array in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "pop()",
      "shift()",
      "splice()",
      "remove()"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "pop()"
  },
  {
    question: "9. What does the 'JSON' stand for in JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Java Standard Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Oriented Network",
      "Java Syntax Object Naming"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    question: "10. How does JavaScript handle asynchronous operations?",
    choices: [
      "Using promises",
      "Using callbacks",
      "Using async/await",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "11. How can you store data in the browser's local storage using JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "localStorage.setItem('key', 'value')",
      "localStorage.save('key', 'value')",
      "localStorage.store('key', 'value')",
      "localStorage.add('key', 'value')"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "localStorage.setItem('key', 'value')"
  }
];
